<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Silvia Papalini</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/</link><atom:link href="https://silviapapalini.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Silvia Papalini</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://silviapapalini.github.io/media/icon_hu3434e75fda98e98001121022ebf30715_650_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Silvia Papalini</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/</link></image><item><title>A Window Into The Hungry Brain: from Pavlovian to avoidance learning.</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/talk/a-window-into-the-hungry-brain-from-pavlovian-to-avoidance-learning./</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/talk/a-window-into-the-hungry-brain-from-pavlovian-to-avoidance-learning./</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mindful Eating Course</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/talk/mindful-eating-course/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/talk/mindful-eating-course/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Overnight fasting affects avoidance learning and relief</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/fasting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/fasting/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Experimental models in psychopathology research: The relation between Research Domain Criteria and Experimental Psychopathology</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/criteria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/criteria/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The drive for thinness: Towards a mechanistic understanding of avoidance behaviors in a non-clinical population</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/thinness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/thinness/</guid><description/></item><item><title>A short-term musical training affects implicit emotion regulation only in behaviour but not in brain activity</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/musical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/musical/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Probiotics-induced changes in gut microbial composition and its effects on cognitive performance after stress: exploratory analyses</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/probiotics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/probiotics/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The role of context in persistent avoidance and the predictive value of relief</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/persistent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/persistent/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dopamine: From prediction error to psychotherapy</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/dopamine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/dopamine/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Reward Anticipation in Early Expression of Psychotic Disorder: A Functional MRI Approach</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/expression/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/expression/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Slides</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/slides/example/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/slides/example/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="create-slides-in-markdown-with-wowchemy">Create slides in Markdown with Wowchemy&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wowchemy&lt;/a> | &lt;a href="https://owchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li>
&lt;li>3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Supports speaker notes&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="controls">Controls&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Next: &lt;code>Right Arrow&lt;/code> or &lt;code>Space&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Previous: &lt;code>Left Arrow&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Start: &lt;code>Home&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Finish: &lt;code>End&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Overview: &lt;code>Esc&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Speaker notes: &lt;code>S&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fullscreen: &lt;code>F&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Zoom: &lt;code>Alt + Click&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PDF Export&lt;/a>: &lt;code>E&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="code-highlighting">Code Highlighting&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Inline code: &lt;code>variable&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Code block:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-python">porridge = &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;
if porridge == &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;:
print(&amp;quot;Eating...&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="math">Math&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Block math:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="fragments">Fragments&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>Press &lt;code>Space&lt;/code> to play!&lt;/p>
&lt;span class="fragment " >
One
&lt;/span>
&lt;span class="fragment " >
**Two**
&lt;/span>
&lt;span class="fragment " >
Three
&lt;/span>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>class&lt;/code>: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>weight&lt;/code>: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="speaker-notes">Speaker Notes&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-markdown">{{% speaker_note %}}
- Only the speaker can read these notes
- Press `S` key to view
{{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>Press the &lt;code>S&lt;/code> key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p>
&lt;aside class="notes">
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Press &lt;code>S&lt;/code> key to view&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/aside>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="themes">Themes&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
data-background-image="/media/boards.jpg"
>
&lt;h2 id="custom-slide">Custom Slide&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-markdown">{{&amp;lt; slide background-image=&amp;quot;/media/boards.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide background-color=&amp;quot;#0000FF&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide class=&amp;quot;my-style&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="custom-css-example">Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Create &lt;code>assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code> with:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-css">.reveal section h1,
.reveal section h2,
.reveal section h3 {
color: navy;
}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h1 id="questions">Questions?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/discussions" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ask&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Stress matters: Randomized controlled trial on the effect of probiotics on neurocognition</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/stress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/stress/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Avoid food to control fear</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/anorexia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/anorexia/</guid><description>&lt;p>Individuals suffering from Anorexia Nervosa (AN) express clinical fear of gain weight and adopt extreme (life-threatening) avoidance behaviors that aim to maintain or reduce body weight. Differently from healthy individuals, in AN hunger seems to be perceived as a threat rather than a motivational drive for food intake. Hence, the anorexic subject avoids food and increases avoidance behaviors (e.g. exercising) to prevent /control the consequences of hunger (i.e. weight gain). Unlike excessive avoidance that characterizes other anxiety-related psychopathologies, excessive avoidance in AN has been often conceptualized as a personality trait (harm avoidance). Yet, a deeper mechanistic understanding of avoidance behaviors in AN is missing in literature. In this project, we are employing an avoidance-relief task (ART) to investigate the presence of excessive avoidance (and the possible over-reinforcing effects of relief on its course) in individuals with a diagnosis of AN.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The neurocircuitry of relief in pathological avoidance</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/ocd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/ocd/</guid><description>&lt;p>Many compulsions displayed by obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD) patients serve to protect against perceived threat and can therefore be conceptualized as ‘avoidance responses’. Exposure treatment with response prevention (ET+RP) is aimed at exposing patients to their obsessive thoughts and perceived threats, while preventing engagement in compulsive avoidant responses. This induces extinction of threat perception and fearful arousal and hence reduces the motivation to avoid. While successful in many patients, however, as much as 40% dropout during treatment or display persistent avoidance after ET+RP. There is a clear need for treatment improvement for these often highly disabled patients.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Improving ET+RP outcomes requires a deeper understanding of the mechanisms that drive excessive and persistent avoidance in OCD patients. Psychological theories ascribe an important role to the relief that follows avoidance when the anticipated threat is successfully averted. This positive feeling arguably functions as a reward to reinforce the foregoing avoidance actions. Indeed, fMRI studies have found that the neurocircuitry of relief overlaps with that of reward, including the ventral tegmental area [VTA], ventral striatum [Nuclei Accumbens] and orbitofrontal cortex [OFC]. This project tests the hypothesis that excessive-persistent avoidance is linked to exaggerated activation of the relief circuitry in OCD participants. For this purpose, we are acquiring functional (and at rest) brain images of OCD and healthy participants in an MRI scanner while they perform a computer task that is designed to model avoidance learning and relief.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The power of hunger</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/fasting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/fasting/</guid><description>&lt;p>In clinical practice, there is a high need to improve the efficacy and long-term outcome of treatments for excessive avoidance and pathological anxiety. This project pinpoints fasting as an emerging, low cost, and safe adjunct to psychotherapy, which effects on behavior and cognition remain, however, to be clarified.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Emerging evidence indicates that fasting triggers a cascade of chemical events able to sensitize the mesolimbic dopaminergic brain, the system which tunes learning signals. Consequently, this project investigates the effects of overnight fasting (16h) on two different dopamine-based types of learning, both highly relevant in anxiety-related disorders: instrumental avoidance learning and fear extinction learning. Given that fasting enhances the representational value of a reward (i.e. food and money), we are additionally examining if the effects of fasting transfer to other types of reinforcers, as so, to relief from threat omission. Specifically, since exaggerating relief from threat omission might over-reinforce instrumental avoidance in the clinical population, in this study we examine is fasting increases relief, and, consequently, avoidance behaviors.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Behavioral pattern separation and its link to the neural mechanisms of fear generalization</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/separation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/separation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Influences of Prolonged Fasting on Behavioral and Brain Patterns</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/prolonged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/prolonged/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mindfulness Eating</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/mindfulness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/mindfulness/</guid><description>&lt;p>What is mindfulness eating?
&amp;ldquo;Mindful eating involves paying full attention to the experience of eating and drinking, both inside and outside the body&amp;hellip;We notice how eating affects our mood and how our emotions like anxiety influence our eating. Gradually we regain the sense of ease and freedom with eating that we had in childhood. It is our natural birthright.&amp;rdquo; (cit. by Jan Chozen Bays and Char Wilkins).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I was introduced to Mindfulness Eating by Caroline Baerten, one of the most inspiring persons I ever met in my life. She followed me during my course in Mindful Based Stress Reduction (MBRS) in Brussel, and, as simple it might sound, I found myself fully connected to the ZEN-based philosophy of this practice. I then felt that a formative mindful path that was closer to my research interest, passions, and values, was really needed. Hence, I flew to Norway where I had the immense pleasure to attend the Mindful Eating-Conscious Living training with Jan Chozen Bays and Char Wilkins (&lt;a href="https://me-cl.com/our-story/%29" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://me-cl.com/our-story/)&lt;/a>, the greatest experience of my life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My wish for the future? To reach excellent research output that can be used to improve the results of this valuable practice.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>About the course:
If you are struggling with food craving, you often experience emotional eating when stresses or anxious, you are you curios and do you simply want to experience a different approach to food, this 8 weeks program might be of your interest. Mindful Eating is a non-diet approach to achieve a healthier relationship with food and your body.
The participation depends upon medical-related conditions. If interested to participate and/or need further information please check the contact section of the website&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/admin/config.yml</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/admin/config.yml</guid><description/></item><item><title>A Window Into The Hungry Brain: overnight fasting effects on the neurobiology of avoidance learning and relief -- Scientific paper in preparation</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/fasting_fmri/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/fasting_fmri/</guid><description>&lt;p>Scientific paper in preparation&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="my-accademic-path">My accademic path&lt;/h2>
&lt;figure class="floatright" >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img alt="" srcset="
/about/silvia_hu919e1f5988953d270124f7d811fab6e8_1146442_5ff89391ecd3b62b62c59e0555ae413d.webp 400w,
/about/silvia_hu919e1f5988953d270124f7d811fab6e8_1146442_3a539c92adc1d44bcdb44d79d914bf94.webp 760w,
/about/silvia_hu919e1f5988953d270124f7d811fab6e8_1146442_1200x1200_fit_q75_h2_lanczos.webp 1200w"
src="https://silviapapalini.github.io/about/silvia_hu919e1f5988953d270124f7d811fab6e8_1146442_5ff89391ecd3b62b62c59e0555ae413d.webp"
width="529"
height="760"
loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>I hold a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Experimental Psychology and obtained my first Ph.D. in Psychological Sciences at the University of Florence (UniFi), Italy, conducting basic research on reward-related brain processes in humans. I developed my scientific knowledge on reward-processing and neuroimaging skills also working in collaboration with the Maastricht University (The Netherlands) via an Erasmus+ European grant. In 2016, I became a member of the &amp;lsquo;Food and Cognition group&amp;rsquo; at the Donders Institute (The Netherlands) where I investigated the effects of a probiotic diet on neuro-cognition and stress, with a focus on cognitive control mechanisms. In 2018, I started a second Ph.D. at KULeuven with the aim to translate knowledge from fundamental research to the clinical field.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="my-research">My research&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The final aim of my research is to help people that struggle with excessive anxiety and emotional (non)eating. I am fascinated by the bidirectional relationship between food and learning. Currently, I am investigating the effects of overnight fasting and the role of dopamine-mediated mechanisms (i.e., relief) on conditioning, error-based learning, and instrumental avoidance. I am conducting research in healthy individuals as well as in individuals with pathological control and excessive avoidance behaviors (i.e., anorexia nervosa and obsessive-compulsive disorder). In my research, I like to apply an interdisciplinary approach, integrating behavioral research, nutritional science, and neuroimaging (3TfMRI). To transfer my scientific knowledge to the applied field I have participated in the Mindful Eating professional training (ME-CL1) and became a Mindful Eating teacher in training.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="my-future-aspirations-as-researcher">My future aspirations as researcher&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Currently, I am a European Research Council (ERC) starting grant aspirant/applicant. If founded, my ERC project will focus on the fundamental learning processes underpinning excessive emotional eating.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Impaired Action-Safety Learning And Excessive Relief During Elevated Avoidance In Anxiety Patients -- Scientific paper in preparation</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/avoidance_leiden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/avoidance_leiden/</guid><description>&lt;p>Scientific paper in preparation&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Roots in Nature</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/roots-in-nature/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/roots-in-nature/</guid><description>
&lt;figure class="floatright" >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img alt="" srcset="
/roots-in-nature/olives_hu3d0adf75ebe5eb1f1e03d77c00bb3087_386283_db2a0959c0a9be4c5f8c8529f342225b.webp 400w,
/roots-in-nature/olives_hu3d0adf75ebe5eb1f1e03d77c00bb3087_386283_36e050ab4cd293473a96ddf9232fb35c.webp 760w,
/roots-in-nature/olives_hu3d0adf75ebe5eb1f1e03d77c00bb3087_386283_1200x1200_fit_q75_h2_lanczos.webp 1200w"
src="https://silviapapalini.github.io/roots-in-nature/olives_hu3d0adf75ebe5eb1f1e03d77c00bb3087_386283_db2a0959c0a9be4c5f8c8529f342225b.webp"
width="570"
height="760"
loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>In many ways, my approach to research and interest in mindful eating are connected to Nature.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Nature might seem something far away from a scientist who spends most of her time in the LAB, but that is only partially true. Fortunately, I had the greatest luck to grow up in a beautiful and peaceful place (Castell&amp;rsquo;Azzara) in the middle of Italy, and to stay close to the work of one of my best teachers in life: my brother, Leo.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Leo cultivates olive trees and produces fresh olive oil every year. His love and respect for Nature are so deeply honest that it is difficult to do not get inspired by the way he does his job (I would better call it passion or value). Leo is interested in learning how to help grow and reproduce the olive trees, follows courses to learn about the best ways of pruning in its geographic region, checks his olive trees every day to be sure they get enough water and nutrients that can protect them from diseases when seasons change or are particularly harsh. In few words, Leo built up his own LAB. I followed his teaching, picking &amp;lsquo;my own&amp;rsquo; trees of interest (people), but maintaining that way of connecting with and caring for nature.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The fresh olive oil comes from his hard work of harvest in November (about 300 plants) when I and the rest of the family are trying to help him with some manual work. Yes, I said manual. Why? Leo wants to avoid damaging the trees during their production with aggressive machines that could break their branches. The olives are picked carefully, and brought as soon as possible to the local oil mill to avoid the formation of molds and bacteria. Once the olive oil is ready, he checks its color, odor, and density. He tastes the olive oil with all his senses, in silent connection with his body. My brother is a great mindful eating teacher on his own LAB and he doesn&amp;rsquo;t know (and doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to). During my mindful eating training in Norway, I could see a strong parallel between my brother&amp;rsquo;s way to relate to food and eating and the teaching of the masters. It felt very familiar.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Nature, the eternal mother, is a great place to find answers if you are connected it to it; that&amp;rsquo;s what Leo would tell me when difficult questions arise in life, either scientific or personal.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The predictive value of neural reward processing on exposure therapy outcome: Results from a randomized controlled trial</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/exposure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/publication/exposure/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>