<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects | Silvia Papalini</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/</link><atom:link href="https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Projects</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://silviapapalini.github.io/media/icon_hu3434e75fda98e98001121022ebf30715_650_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Projects</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/</link></image><item><title>Severo.jl</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/severo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/severo/</guid><description>&lt;p>Severo.jl was created for the scalable analysis of single-cell RNA-seq datasets: the implementation is designed to minimize hardware resources such as memory while maximizing performance through parallelism and hardware optimizations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Severo.jl gives an order of magnitude speedup when compared to other existing packages such as Seurat and Scanpy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The package provides a toolbox of different algorithms and statistical methods from which the user can pick and choose.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Avoid food to control fear</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/hpc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/hpc/</guid><description>&lt;p>Individuals suffering from Anorexia Nervosa (AN) express clinical fear of gain weight and adopt extreme (life-threatening) avoidance behaviors that aim to maintain or reduce body weight. Differently from healthy individuals, in AN hunger seems to be perceived as a threat rather than a motivational drive for food intake. Hence, the anorexic subject avoids food and increases avoidance behaviors (e.g. exercising) to prevent /control the consequences of hunger (i.e. weight gain). Unlike excessive avoidance that characterizes other anxiety-related psychopathologies, excessive avoidance in AN has been often conceptualized as a personality trait (harm avoidance). Yet, a deeper mechanistic understanding of avoidance behaviors in AN is missing in literature. In this project, we are employing an avoidance-relief task (ART) to investigate the presence of excessive avoidance (and the possible over-reinforcing effects of relief on its course) in individuals with a diagnosis of AN.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The power of hunger</title><link>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/diffmem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://silviapapalini.github.io/project/diffmem/</guid><description>&lt;p>In clinical practice, there is a high need to improve the efficacy and long-term outcome of treatments for excessive avoidance and pathological anxiety. This project pinpoints fasting as an emerging, low cost, and safe adjunct to psychotherapy, which effects on behavior and cognition remain, however, to be clarified.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Emerging evidence indicates that fasting triggers a cascade of chemical events able to sensitize the mesolimbic dopaminergic brain, the system which tunes learning signals. Consequently, this project investigates the effects of overnight fasting (16h) on two different dopamine-based types of learning, both highly relevant in anxiety-related disorders: instrumental avoidance learning and fear extinction learning. Given that fasting enhances the representational value of a reward (i.e. food and money), we are additionally examining if the effects of fasting transfer to other types of reinforcers, as so, to relief from threat omission. Specifically, since exaggerating relief from threat omission might over-reinforce instrumental avoidance in the clinical population, in this study we examine is fasting increases relief, and, consequently, avoidance behaviors.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>